http://www.animalclinic.com/privacy-policy/

The Animal Clinic - 701 Broadway St. Galveston, TX 77550 | P: 409-763-6484 | F: 409-763-4023
HomeAbout Our TeamVirtual TourJoin Our TeamServices Wellness and Sick VisitsSurgeryDentistryDigital RadiographyUltrasoundBoarding/ GroomingWalk-in’sWe See ExoticsOnline Forms And Links Online PharmacyRequest AppointmentMedication / Food RequestBoarding FormDrop Off FormNew Client RegistrationSign up to get our AppThe Cat ClinicAdopt MeContactMore Info NewsPet Care Video LibraryHurricane NoticeSuccess StoriesPet Memorials
MenuHomeAboutOur TeamVirtual TourJoin Our TeamServicesWellness and Sick VisitsSurgeryDentistryDigital RadiographyUltrasoundBoarding/ GroomingWalk-in’sWe See ExoticsOnline Forms And LinksOnline PharmacyRequest AppointmentMedication / Food RequestBoarding FormDrop Off FormNew Client RegistrationSign up to get our AppThe Cat ClinicAdopt MeContactMore InfoNewsPet Care Video LibraryHurricane NoticeSuccess StoriesPet Memorials
Get DirectionsPrivacy PolicyAnimal Clinic built the Petcue[App name] app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Animal Clinic at no cost and is intended for use as is.This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Petcue[App name] unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.Information Collection and UseFor a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to GPS location. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.The app does use third-party services that may collect information used to identify you.Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the appGoogle Play ServicesOne SignalLog DataWe want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (b
IPb
) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.CookiesCookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device’s internal memory.This Service does not use these cookies explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use cookies to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.Service ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:To facilitate our Service;To provide the Service on our behalf;To perform Service-related services; orTo assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.SecurityWe value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links to Other SitesThis Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyThese Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.This policy is effective as of 2020-07-19Contact UsIf you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at animalclinic.com.
American Veterinary Medical AssociationVeterinary PartnerClinic HoursDayOpenClosedMonday7:30 am 	 	  5:30 pmTuesday7:30 am 	 	  5:30 pmWednesday7:30 am 	 	  5:30 pmThursday7:30 am 	 	  5:30 pmFriday7:30 am 	 	  5:30 pmSaturday9:00 am 	 	  1:00 pmSundayClosed 	 	  Closed Let's Stay Connected:
Like Us On Facebook
The Animal Clinic
Galveston, TX Animal Hospital
701 Broadway St.,
Galveston,
TX
77550
(409) 763-6484
Veterinary Website by Doctor MultimediaAccessibility | Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy
Close
Font Resize
A-
A+
Keyboard navigation
Readable FontContrast
Choose color
black
Close
AccessibilityBoarding FormDrop Off FormFacebookGoogle+Hurricane NoticeMedication / Food RequestNew Client RegistrationNewsOnline FormsPet Care Video LibraryPet MemorialsPetCuePrivacy PolicySally’s FundSign up to get our AppSuccess StoriesTerms & ConditionsWe See ExoticsCallAbout UsDirectionsServicesDentistryDigital RadiographySurgeryWellness and Sick VisitsBoarding/ GroomingWalk-in’sUltrasoundCold Laser TherapyThe Cat ClinicAppointmentsOur TeamNew ClientsSpecialsContact UsVirtual TourAdopt Me
